Guide to the Yale University Library Records Concerning Redevelopment of Sterling Memorial Library and Construction of the Cross Campus Library
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Yale University Library records concerning redevelopment of Sterling Memorial Library and construction of the Cross Campus Library
1967-1971
RU 807
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
0.75
(2 boxes)
The records consist of plans, minutes, and cost estimates documenting the construction of the Cross Campus Library and the redevelopment of Sterling Memorial Library at Yale.
Yale University. Library
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 46-B (YRG 46-B), Records and materials documenting individual Yale buildings, facilities, and grounds.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of plans, minutes, and cost estimates documenting the construction of the Cross Campus Library and the redevelopment of Sterling Memorial Library at Yale.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by record type.
Academic libraries -- Design and construction; College buildings -- Design and construction; Yale University -- Buildings; Yale University. Library
- Records concerning Sterling redevelopment and the Cross Campus Library, 1967-1971; Accession 19ND-A-244
  - March 1968 - December 1969 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - January - December 1970 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - January - October 1971 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Cross Campus Library (CCL) - Cost Estimations (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Department Heads Meetings July 8-July 30,1968 (CCL) (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Detail Planning' (eeL) (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Furniture (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Sterling Redevelopment - Bldgs and Grounds Planning File (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Sterling Redevelopment - Current File (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Sterling Redevelopment - Public Reactions (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Sterling Redevelopment - Sterling Library Annex (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Sterling Redevelopment - Summaries of July 1968 Dept. Heads Meeting on Building Program (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Sterling Redevelopment - J. Tanis' File (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Sterling Redevelopment - Space Planning - Logistics for Cross Campus (Box 2, Folder 14)